{
    "id": "d26c278cd0154c768559f9a9f444c141",
    "title": "Good and well grammar worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "aac6d219d9a54aeca615713046ef972e",
            "title": "Good and Well | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Your daughter sings ………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a ……………. writer.",
                    "description": "Good is an adjective. We use it before a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is a …………….. built engine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a …………….. friend.",
                    "description": "Good is an adjective well is an adverb. Adjectives go before nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t speak English …………….., but I can make myself understood.",
                    "description": "Here the adverb well modifies the verb speak.",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am not feeling very ……………. today.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Only a ………….. teacher can teach English ………………",
                    "description": "Here the adjective good modifies the noun teacher and the adverb well modifies the verb teach.",
                    "answers": [
                        "good, good",
                        "good, well",
                        "well, well",
                        "well, good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her style is …………….",
                    "description": "Here the adjective good acts as the complement of the subject. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I like that design. It is ……………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The car runs .........................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}